Believe in the impossible. Believe in each other.
The Boys in the Boat is a drama, history film directed by George Clooney.
The triumphant underdog story of the University of Washington men's rowing team,
who stunned the world by competing at the 1936 Berlin Olympics.
Coach Al Ulbrickson, played by Joel Edgerton.
Joe Rantz, played by Callum Turner.
George Pocock, played by Peter Guinness.
Roger Morris, played by Sam Strike.
Chuck Day, played by Thomas Elms.
Don Hume, played by Jack Mulhern.
The Boys in the Boat is a 2023 American biographical sports drama film
produced and directed by George Clooney from a screenplay by Mark L.
Smith, based on the 2013 book by Daniel James Brown.
The film follows the University of Washington rowing team, and
their quest to compete in the 1936 Summer Olympics.
It stars Joel Edgerton as coach Al Ulbrickson Sr.
and Callum Turner as rower Joe Rantz.
The Boys in the Boat had its world premiere in Los Angeles on December 11, 2023, and was theatrically released
by Amazon MGM Studios in the United States on December 25 and internationally by Warner Bros.
It  grossed $55 million and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of sports, olympic games, rowing, 1930s, dignified.
The tone is uplifting and emotional.